Downloaded @ subs4free.club
I wonder if she'll come
back again.
I wonder if she comes
again.
I wonder if she'll
come back again.
I wonder if she comes again.
I wonder if she'll come
back again.
I wonder if she comes
again. I wonder...
I wonder if she comes tonight.
I wonder what games we'll play.
If she comes again tonight,
Okay, that sounds fun.
Her name's Alice. She's six.
Ready or not, here I come.
Liam?
Where are you?
Liam, you're sleep walking
again.
There you are, next to my
sister.
This isn't funny!
I'm gonna tell mom!
Liam, you're scaring me.
Get away from me!
Liam, stop it!
Alice! Help me! Alice!
Alice
so why don't you tell me...
A little bit about your
nightmare?
Male patient
I first saw it as a child...
Standing in the shadows at the
end of my bed.
It's hard to describe
what it looks like.
This figure in the darkness.
It didn't have a face.
Female patient
I wake up. I can't move.
Like I'm paralyzed.
Male ♪2 the room gets
darker and darker.
That's when I know it's coming.
Female ♪2
it happens to me every night.
I don't wanna sleep any more.
Male ♪3 and there's this
pressure on my chest...
This huge force.
It's like something's holding
you down.
I feel terrified.
Female ♪3
I knew it was there.
I could feel it in the darkness
just... watching me.
Man ♪4
I feel trapped.
I wasn't able to move any part
of my body.
I could only move my eyes
back and forth.
Female ♪4
and then I saw this figure...
Coming towards me and I...
I couldn't make it out,
because it was black.
Man ♪5 you'd be surprised how
many people are affected.
I think some people don't even
like to talk about it.
Female ♪5
every fiber of your body...
Is telling you it's something
evil.
Male ♪6 it looks like this old
woman, a haggard old woman...
With these cold, dark eyes.
It's not like a nightmare,
it's... it's something else.
Female ♪6 it had such power.
I felt completely helpless.
You don't know what it's like.
It's like a curse.
Male ♪7 you wanna run,
you wanna scream...
But it won't let you.
The thing was well
over six foot.
Female ♪7
I think it was seven feet tall.
Male ♪8 it was like this
moving darkness.
Female ♪8 it was the greatest
terror I've ever experienced.
Male ♪9
the shadow man is violent.
Female ♪9
the hag, she takes hold of me..
And I think I'm gonna die.
Male ♪10 well, you know
it's coming back.
It is always coming back
for you.
Boy's voice
Alice!
Were your dreams sweet, mummy?
Not as sweet as you.
Good morning.
One, two, three.
Always, always, always.
Has Henry had his breakfast yet?
He had six peanuts!
Six.
Oh, six.
You ready for your test?
Yeah.
Ah, excuse me.
Yes!
Who's this?
Erm, it's you. You're flying.
Oh, super mom!
It's very nice.
Where am I flying to?
I don't know. Nowhere, I guess.
Do you like it?
I love it.
One, two, three.
Oh, my gosh, every time.
Loser!
You can't kiss the artist!
Yes, I can!
Okay, artist, time to go!
Michelle
and I kept trying to breathe...
And I couldn't breathe...
And I was telling myself, like,
Michelle, wake-up.
Wake-up. Breathe. Get out
of bed. Move.
Like, do something, you're
okay, but I couldn't.
So, in turn, her brain
is not allowing her...
To go into rem-deep sleep.
This is what's causing her
parasomnia episodes...
Sleep talking, scary night
terrors.
Seeing things that aren't
really there, yeah.
You know, it's a lot more common
condition than you might think.
Even my own daughter, she goes
through this sometimes.
And because of what we know now,
it's easily treatable.
Hm, today's dream drawing:
Who is it?
It's meant to be me, flying.
Hm, floating more like.
If I drew my dreams,
I'd get arrested.
That's because you're a
sociopath, Malcolm.
Shh, they'll hear.
What about you?
What about me?
What creepy things have you got
lurking in your dreams?
Dr. arnolds, the morgans
have arrived.
I thought they weren't coming
until 3:00?
I told them they were early, but
they seemed a little... on edge.
Okay.
Why don't you tell me a little
bit about what's been going on?
Erm, about two months ago our
baby boy, he...
He passed away... in his sleep.
Let it go.
Stop it!
Charlie... please.
I'm so sorry.
Um, around the same time,
we started to find Daniel, um...
Sleepwalking and... and sleep
talking...
Sometimes even screaming.
He's had episodes like this
before.
But then we started to find him
asleep, we think...
But with his eyes open,
chest heaving, trying to talk...
But his whole body's paralyzed.
Daniel, you've been experiencing
sleep paralysis.
That's when you think
you're awake...
But your brain is still
dreaming.
You can open your eyes
and look around the room...
But your body can't move,
because you're still asleep.
You feel trapped.
Your mind tells you that there's
something else in the room.
Something bad, something
pressing down on your chest.
It's all up here, honey.
It's all in our imagination.
I know it can be scary, but
there are no ghosts or goblins.
See, honey, what did
I tell you? Huh?
Why don't both of you come
and get one of these? Mm.
What do you say?
Here, sweetie.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Losing a loved one, as you
both know...
Can take a very heavy
psychological toll...
Especially on children.
So I wouldn't be surprised
if this tragedy...
Acted as a trigger for Daniel's
nocturnal behavior.
But, you know, we will run some
tests while he's here and...
You know, I wouldn't worry.
I haven't run into a single
person...
Who's issues haven't been
resolvable.
But it's not just him.
We've all started having these
terrible dreams.
Sleepwalking and sleep talking.
I'm sorry, I'm confused...
Which one of you is staying
with us tomorrow night?
All of us.
Okay.
Thank you, my dear.
You're welcome. Goodnight.
Goodnight, Mr. futterman.
And when gretel opened her
apron, the pearls...
And precious stones were
scattered all over the room...
And hansel took one handful
after another out of his pocket.
Then was all care at an end and
they lived happily ever after.
When the witch died, did she
go to heaven?
Not everybody gets into heaven.
Only the good people, like your
baby brother.
Time for bed, Daniel.
I don't wanna go to sleep.
Then why don't you do your
multiplication tables...
Like the nice doctor said.
So you won't think about
the bad things.
I don't want it to come again.
Oh, sweetie, that's just
a nightmare...
But this is a good, strong
house...
With good, strong, brave
children.
Show me the money.
Grrr. Mini muscle man.
Can Alfie sleep with us tonight?
Sure.
Love you both. Sleep tight.
Dr. arnolds!
Dammit, cam!
Sorry.
Oh, gosh.
I have to get this coffee to
Malcolm in observation.
He's probably having a caffeine
melt-down by now.
Hey, what do you guys do
in that little cave anyway?
The observation room?
We observe.
Oh, that's genius.
Two times three is six.
Three times three, nine.
Four times three, twelve.
Five times three, fifteen.
Six times three, eighteen.
Maybe it's safer if I stay
on the couch tonight?
You know, just in case...
No, I want you here.
Close to me.
It's gonna be okay,
we'll figure it out.
What?
Alice, you all right?
Yeah... yeah, I was just resting
my eyes and I...
Um, I nodded off.
Why don't you go home?
I have this covered.
Thanks, Malcolm.
Hey. Hey.
No, no, they're gonna get me.
They're gonna get me.
Don't want them to get me.
I don't wanna die.
Daddy needs a smoothie.
Daddy needs...
Your daddy needs a smoothie.
It's you... yeah, that's right.
I don't want it to get me.
I don't want it to come again.
That's right, who is daddy's
boy? It's you.
I don't want it to come again.
I don't want it to get me.
Hey, boo-boo.
Hey, boo-boo-boo.
I hate you.
I hate you!
Mommy... help me.
Why?
I don't want it to get me.
What's wrong with my teeth?
I hate you!
Emily, wake up!
Wake up.
Daniel...
Dad!
Here's your picture, mom.
So what did you dream
about this time?
Niamh!
Sorry.
It's okay. It's okay, honey.
It's just an accident.
Just grab your school bag.
You...?
Fine.
Hey.
Hey, what's going on?
I'm just tired.
There was a boy yesterday, and
he reminded me of my brother.
Hey, why don't you go back
to bed for a while, huh?
You probably only slept
a couple of hours?
Ready or not, here I come.
Liam?
There you are, next to my
sister.
No, Liam, there's no one there.
It's just me.
Liam!
Alice! Help me!
Alice! Alice!
You two will be sleeping
in here with your parents...
So you'll feel nice and safe,
okay?
What's that?
That is a polysomnogram device.
It helps us figure out why
you're not sleeping properly.
And this monitors your brain
waves...
Your eye movements, your muscle
tone and your breathing.
And this right here measures
your heart rate.
You look like an alien.
That's stupid. She does not.
Well, not a scary alien, right?
Mr. Morgan.
It helps me sleep.
We had another terrible night
last night.
You got no idea how much
we need this to work.
Oh, believe me, I do.
Let's get you back in.
There's a night vision camera
in the corner of the room...
We'll be keeping an eye
on everything...
You do while you sleep.
So will this stop me from
killing all the Teddy bears?
Can't we just never sleep?
Please?
I don't want it to come again.
You don't want what to come
again?
Daniel, we've already talked
about this.
We're the only ones in the room.
Okay? They're just dreams.
We need to get a good night's
sleep.
That's how we're going to get
fixed, sweetie.
Will you help me, Dr. Alice?
Of course I will. That's my job.
Everything's gonna be
fine. See you in the morning.
Did you check
on Mr. futterman?
Yes I did, and he's asleep.
They're definitely shook up.
The father just lost his job.
He seems to be drinking.
And his knuckles...
He says that he's punching the
walls while he's sleep walking..
Which is enough to give
anyone nightmares.
Do you remember the, er,
Mitchell case?
It must have been, well, at
least a decade ago now.
I don't think so.
What was his first name?
Dan Mitchell. He was a farmer
over in winnetka county.
No.
Popular guy by all accounts...
Went to church every Sunday.
Not a bad word to be said
about him.
Anyway, this guy was a chicken
farmer with a few dozen coops.
His family and friends
knew him...
As a sleepwalker and a sleep
worker.
Every night he used to go out...
And do his farm chores while
he slept.
Fill the feeders, sweep the
floor, clean out the muck.
Every night like clockwork.
It sounds pretty useful.
Yeah, maybe to begin with.
Turns out, the whole family had
a history of parasomnia.
One night, while he was seeing
to the chickens in his sleep...
He thought there was an intruder
in his house.
He got into a fight with the
attacker...
Trying to defend his daughter.
By the time they woke him,
it was too late.
He'd hacked his wife to death
with a shovel.
- That's terrible.
- Yeah.
And he was really asleep
when he did it?
Well, he passed all the lie
detector tests.
Even his daughter backed up
the story.
Daniel said he didn't want 'it'
to come again.
What do you think he meant
by that?
Oh, shit, Mr. futterman's gone.
Well, he's probably gone
to the bathroom.
I'll go and check.
Why don't you go and get us
some more coffee.
Mr. futterman?
I fucking told them.
I said no!
No! No! No, no.
No... I... don't...
I don't... I didn't...
I didn't do anything.
Ready or not, here I come.
Alice, guess where I found
futterman?
He was sleep walking in the
shower. Can you believe it?
Daniel?
Daniel!
Malcolm?
Oh, my god.
Daniel, Daniel just breathe.
You're okay. Take it easy,
you're all right.
You'll be okay. Okay, just
breathe. It'll be all right.
That's a good boy.
Take it easy. That's it.
I won't let you!
Let go of me!
Dad, no! Stop!
Give him back.
Dad! Stop!
Alice, are you okay?
I don't think he knew
what he was doing.
Alice.
I think he was sleep walking.
Alice, imagine
if it was one of his kids...
He grabbed by the throat,
or hacked up with a shovel!
You saw the bruises
on Daniel's chest.
That man might not be
consciously abusive...
But he's an alcoholic,
he's dangerous...
And he shouldn't be around them.
This was the right thing to do.
Alice, you should go home.
Be with your family. God...
Forget about this for now.
Oh!
What the hell are you doing?
Niamh!
You need to stay
home and rest.
I'm fine.
You're not fine.
I am.
You do not... fine.
You were saying 'help me'...
Over and over in your sleep
last night.
It was just a dream.
It's not a big deal.
Alice, you were attacked.
It's a big fucking deal!
Christ...
Alice, what are you doing here?
Come here and take a look
at this.
Fascinating...
They're all in rem sleep, but
it's like they're synchronized.
Like puppets.
Hm.
Yeah, except for Daniel.
They all seem to be moving
away from him.
I've never seen such an intense
sleep paralysis episode before.
He looks terrified.
Hey. Hey, guys. I just wanted
to let you know...
I don't work for the hospital
anymore.
I, er, handed in my resignation,
so...
What?
Dr. arnolds, would you mind
a word outside?
Of course.
Nurse paging
Dr. Davies. Dr. Davies, please.
Cam, are you okay?
Look, stay away from that
family.
Never see them again.
Cam... cam, what are you...?
What's that?
Oh, nothing, honey.
Boring stuff.
Work stuff.
I'm sorry I yelled at you
this morning.
It's okay.
Let's get into your
pj's, Danny.
Did your father do this to you,
Daniel?
Then who did?
I told you already... it only
comes when I'm dreaming.
From the shadows.
I don't want it to get me.
Get away from me!
Oh, my god.
Emily... wake up. Wake up.
Mummy, what's going on?
Close your eyes, sweetie.
Close your eyes.
What's going on?
Mom, I don't want
to stay here.
Ssh! Don't move, honey.
Daniel! Daniel!
No! Agh!
Daniel!
Honey?
Hey.
I'm having that nightmare again.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because something about this
feels different.
I just... I...
I heard that little girl singing
the same lullaby...
That Liam sung the night
that he died and I just erm...
I feel like I'm losing my mind.
Hey... it's stress,
that's all it is, it's stress.
Hm?
I thought about what you said...
And you're right.
I need to slow down,
and I need to get some sleep.
So I'm gonna go into work and
I'm gonna ask for some time off.
Hallelujah.
Dr. arnolds! Please.
You know he didn't mean
to attack you.
You don't understand.
It... it isn't Charlie, it's
something else. Something...
I think it's trying to pull us
apart so it can...
Can what?
I think it's trying to kill
my son.
Mrs. Morgan, no one is trying
to kill your son.
Your husband...
My husband was trying to protect
us and you got him locked up!
Last night, Emily butchered
our dog...
With a pair of garden shears,
in her sleep, for god sake!
I saw something lift my son's
bed off the ground.
I need my husband.
I need my husband back!
You said you would help us!
How could you do this to us?
You know, that night
in the ward. I can't...
I can't explain it.
There was something in the room
with us.
I had to stop it. I'm sorry.
You know, people all over the
world, they describe the same...
Dark presence during sleep
paralysis episodes.
We write it off as hypnagogic
hallucinations, but...
I knew it wanted Daniel and it
sure as shit wasn't no dream.
I hate you!
I hate you. I hate you.
Emily?
Oh, no, oh, god... Sarah.
It's steak.
Oh...
Agh!
Sarah! Sarah, wake up!
Sarah, it's me.
Hey! Help me, please.
Daniel.
Daniel! Daniel! Daniel!
Help me! Daniel! Get in here.
Daniel! Daniel!
Is he... okay?
Wake him up! Wake him up!
Daniel, wake up!
Wake up, Daniel!
Niamh dream, dream,
dream, dream, dream.
Alice?
Hm.
Honey?
Alice?
Oh...
I'm sorry. How's Daniel?
He's fine... for now.
Look, erm, we can't go
to the hospital.
What can we do?
I don't know.
He's gotta be here.
Cam?
Cam, it's Alice.
It's Dr. arnolds, from the
hospital.
Cam?
Alice.
Alice, how did you...
I'm... I'm sorry, I can't help
you. Please, you gotta go.
Just leave.
My son's life is in danger!
Please.
You're not gonna like
what I have to say.
Go back home and distance
ourself from this family.
And, I'm afraid your son
is going to die.
There is nothing you can do.
What, that's it?
Yes. Now, I'm sorry,
you gotta go.
I'm not going anywhere!
Leave now!
Cam, don't make me call
the cops on you...
For stealing tranquilizers
from the hospital.
Grandpa? Okay... just a minute.
Hey, just go back to sleep,
okay. Shh... no.
These guys are just leaving.
It's okay.
My grandfather is fine,
Dr. arnolds.
It's just that those drugs...
They're the only way he can
get to sleep.
Your son has always suffered
from sleep talking...
And sleepwalking? Hm?
Yes.
That's how the wretched thing
found him.
It seeks out children who are
neither asleep, nor awake.
For it does not exist in the
'real' world...
Or in the 'dream' world, but in
the cracks in between.
Well, what is it?
Grandpa, please.
Ah!
It's got many names: The ancient
Greek's called it mora...
The persian's bakhtak.
The Japanese kannashibari.
I first heard it called
ocnitsa.
In English...
The night hag.
Yeah.
In olde English, the night-mare.
A demon that has existed since
man first learned to dream.
It doesn't exist, they kept
telling me.
Just in your imagination.
Once a child is chosen...
Then it paralyzes the child...
In its sleep before crushing it.
And then, when it's finished
feasting...
What?!
It happened to me.
Okay, that's enough.
Alice, please, I beg you,
just leave him alone.
How did you survive then?
Another child died in my place.
I don't know how...
I don't know why.
I've spent my whole life
trying to understand.
But the only thing
I've learned...
Is that there are no answers.
There is no help
for your son.
Charlie, look at me.
Nothing is going to happen
to Daniel.
We're gonna do everything
we can. We'll keep him awake.
Whatever we have to do.
There are always answers.
I like you. I, too, was once
fierce.
Then I got old. Life's a bitch.
Life's a b...
Hello.
Are the salts working?
So far, but he's fading.
We should not be here, grandpa.
Hello.
Here, sweetheart.
Hi.
Okay, the oxygen should keep him
awake for a little while.
By now, the thing that
is attacking your son...
Doesn't care whether it's day
or night.
It knows he's weak.
And when he sleeps,
it will come.
We will find a solution,
but until we do...
We all need to stay by him
and keep him awake.
Be strong for your son.
You can do that.
Thank you, Alice.
I used to sleepwalk a lot
when I was boy, too.
It was while I was asleep
that I first saw it.
A kind old woman who would sing
that lullaby.
Come, she said, let's play
a game.
That's how it got close to me.
But then it all changed...
When I first saw it
for what it really was.
Grandpa, stop it.
Tell me, tell me, have you all
been sleepwalking?
Nightmares?
The horse.
The horse with the white eyes.
I hate it.
Nightmares, sleepwalking...
The same thing happened
to my family.
I believe this parasite infects
your dreams.
It knew my family's darkest
fears...
And used their nightmares to
distract them away from me...
Allowing it to feed on me,
undisturbed.
Except for my sister.
She was somehow able to save me
from it.
Then she paid with her own life.
Daniel, wake up!
Get him to the bathroom!
Dan, wake up!
You can wake'm in the bathroom
in the cold water, come on!
Wake up!
Talk to me. Talk to me.
Tell me your name.
Come on.
Charlie, get my medical bag.
I'm not leaving him.
Charlie, now!
Dan, say something! We can't
keep him like this, Alice!
I know. This will keep you up.
Talk to me, Daniel!
Please, Daniel!
Get him up!
Do something!
Oh, my god.
Here we go.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
I'm sorry.
How long will the adrenaline
keep him awake for?
I'm not sure, maybe a couple
hours.
Can we give him more
if we need to?
His pulse is too high.
Alice tom?
Mom, where are you? I miss you.
Oh, honey, I'm just...
I'm busy helping someone.
Alice
is daddy there?
Daddy's in the lounge,
talking to Malcolm.
Niamh I heard them
say you're trying to save...
Your brother... I thought your
brother was dead?
Just tell daddy that, erm,
that everything's fine, okay?
Niamh okay, mom...
Okay.
But please come home soon.
I didn't sleep very well last
night without you here.
I'll be home very soon,
I promise.
Okay. Bye. I love you.
Alice
I love you, too.
Sweet red chili flavor...
They're good.
I'm okay.
I understand that you want
to help...
But you should go home
to your family.
There's nothing more for you
to do.
Do not lose sight of what's
important.
Saving that boy is important.
Saving him is impossible.
What you can do is save
yourself.
Don't make the same mistake
as me.
It drove me to obsession.
I was so scared, I couldn't
sleep for years.
It's crazy what a person
will do to stay awake.
I tried to cut my eyelids off.
Oh, god.
Come on, grandpa, we should go.
You know, I really thought
that you might find an answer.
When you're fixated
on something...
It's as if you're sleepwalking.
Time to wake up.
Amado... do you think that your
sister was sleepwalking...
When she saved you?
Hey, energy drink.
Hey, psst...
You drink this.
One more.
Hey, good boy.
Hey, you remember Christmas
a couple of years back?
Grandma's house?
It snowed hard all
Christmas Eve.
You were so excited about all
your presents...
You couldn't sleep.
You came to sleep
with mom and me.
You just sat there all night,
at the end of the bed.
Your eyes wide open.
Remember?
Do you remember that?
So we know this thing pushes
us away from Daniel...
When it's feeding, right?
So what if we could get back
to Daniel to protect him?
We've been with him before,
we can't stop it.
Yes, but we were awake.
What if we could protect Daniel
while we're asleep?
I know, just follow me.
My brother saw "it" when
he was sleepwalking.
You, Charlie, saw something
at the hospital...
When you were sleepwalking.
Amado's sister not
only saw it...
But she could stop it while
she was sleepwalking.
My sister died.
We're not children, and there's
more than one of us...
So maybe if we can see it,
we can stop it.
Fucking nuts!
You're asking me to protect
my son when I'm asleep!
Charlie, we have to do
something.
Daniel is exhausted and I cannot
give him any more medication.
He'll be asleep soon.
And there's nothing we can do to
stop it, this is our only shot.
We'll know what to expect
this time.
We won't let it push us away.
All right.
But how am I going to get
to sleep?
It's heavy stuff.
It's just for tonight.
So, who's driving, you or me?
Okay.
It's okay, she's safe now.
It's done, Sarah. Give me
your arm, Charlie.
Oh, the demon will use our
nightmares against us...
To draw us away from him.
Do not believe your
surroundings.
Return to this room.
Return to Daniel.
If I fall asleep, will I die?
No, honey, I know you're scared.
I am, too...
But we're going to get through
this together, all right?
Let me test you. This will keep
you awake, okay?
What's... what's... what's three
times five?
Fifteen.
Fifteen, good, and, erm...
What's four times five?
Twe... twenty.
All right, stay with me, honey.
What's six times eight?
Six times...
Daniel? Daniel? Daniel?
Amado, are you awake?
Nothing's happening to me.
Why is no one sleepwalking?
Daniel?
Peter.
Hey, Peter. Hello.
Hey. Come here.
Hello.
Why would you say that
about my teeth? I...
It's not real.
Help me, Alice! Please!
I can't help you.
You can, Alice. Please!
Remember where you are!
Come back!
Come back to Daniel!
Daniel.
Help me, Alice! Please!
I can't help you.
You're not my brother.
Alice!
No, my brother's dead.
Help!
It's Daniel...
Agh! Agh!
Peter.
Oh, no, no! Peter! Peter!
Please!
Liam!
Alice, help me! Alice!
Agh! Agh! Agh!
Peter!
Liam! No!
Please, Alice!
Finish what you started!
Alice! Liam!
Oh, I've got you.
I've got you.
My brother is dead!
Amado?
Finish what I started.
I'm sorry.
You did the right thing.
Finally, I can get some
real sleep.
Hello.
Niamh mom?
Hi! How are you, my little
artist?
Niamh
I'm retired now. Wanna play?
Yes. One, two, three.
One, two, three.
No, that's not fair!
I won!
You cheated.
I did not cheat!
Who's the loser now?
Best out of three.
Okay.
Tom
okay, sweetie, that's enough.
Look, erm, mom and dad need
to talk now, okay?
- One minute only.
- Okay, okay.
- One minute.
- Okay.
I love you.
Niamh
love you, too.
Hey.
How is she?
Apart from her hamster dying
last night...
She's, erm, she's fine.
Oh, that's awful.
Tom
how are you?
I'm really good, actually.
Rested. Wow.
Feeling better, better than I've
been in years.
I don't think that either of us
have, er...
Slept well since this whole
thing happened.
I know. Tom...
This has been so rough on the
two of you and I'm so sorry.
All my priorities were
messed up.
Tom yeah, I know,
it's erm, it's okay.
I promise from now on, you two
are my first priority.
No more obsessing over work.
No.
Tom
Alice? What's wrong, honey?
No. Tom, that lullaby,
where did she hear that?!
Tom
honey, calm down. We're okay.
- Where did she hear it?
- Niamh mom?
Tom
what are you talking about?
What are you...?
Where did she hear it?
Tom
look, please, just calm down!
- Alice?
- Niamh mom?
We're fine. Everything is fine.
No, it's not okay!
Just relax.
Please listen to me.
Okay, niamh! Niamh!
Tom? Please!
You're upsetting niamh!
- I wanna talk to my husband!
- Please just...
- Tom?
- Mom!
Tom!
I... I can't do this anymore!
Please... stop it!
- Tom! Tom! Tom!
- Okay, listen to me...